# Sergey Hmurovich

# Frontend developer

# CONTACTS













<u>Minsk, Belarus</u>



+375297374777



ksn\_i777@mail.ru

# SKILLS



## React

library for building user interfaces



Redux / Redux Toolkit state container for applications



## TypeScript

strongly typed language based on JS



## **JavaScript**

language for web application interactivity



application programming interface



# development application through testing

Storybook environment for developing a library of UI



application version control system



HTML5

Material-UI

library of components for the UI



# document markup language

document style language



# SCSS / SASS

CSS-based metalanguage



# <sub>.</sub> English A2 in progress

# ABOUT ME

I'm a frontend developer with experience developing the visible part of web applications. The main technologies of my work are React, Redux and TypeScript. Every day I improve my skills in this direction and plan to expand them with new technologies, such as React Native and Angular. I'm always open to offers. Tell me more about your needs.

# **PROJECTS**

# LEARNING CARDS - An application to learn anything

stack: React, Redux Toolkit, TS, Axios, Formik, MUI, SASS

# <u>TODOLIST - Task manager</u>

stack: React, Redux Toolkit, TS, Axios, Formik, MUI, TDD

# SOCIAL NETWORK - Online platform for communication

stack: React, Redux, TS, Axios, Redux-form

# **EXPERIENCE**

2022 - present / Part-time

03.2019 - 01.2023 / Full-time

Head of design sector

03.2014 - 02.2019 / Full-time

Design engineer

# **EDUCATION**

2022 / IT-INCUBATOR /

Frontend developer (React, Redux, TS, JS, Rest API, TDD)

2009 - 2015 / A.D.Sakharov ISEU /

Nuclear and radiation safety engineer